Yesterday, all my troubles seemed so far away
昨天，所有的烦恼似乎都离我很远
Now it looks as though they're here to stay
现在看起来它们似乎要留下来
Oh, I believe in yesterday suddenly
噢，我突然相信昨天
I'm not half the man I used to be
我已不再是从前的那个人
There's a shadow hanging over me
有个阴影悬挂在我上面
Oh, yesterday came suddenly
噢，昨天突然来临
Why she had to go?
为什么她不得不离开？
I don't know what she wouldn't say
我不知道她为什么不说
I said something wrong
我说错了什么
Now I look for yesterday
现在我寻找昨天
Yesterday
昨天
Love was such an easy game to play
爱曾是如此容易的游戏
Now I need a place to hide away
现在我需要个地方躲藏
Oh, I believe in yesterday
噢，我突然相信昨天
Why she had to go?
为什么她不得不离开？
I don't know what she wouldn't say
我不知道她为什么不说
I said something wrong
我说错了什么
Now I look for yesterday
现在我寻找昨天
Yesterday
昨天
Love was such an easy game to play
爱曾是如此容易的游戏
Now I need a place to hide away
现在我需要个地方躲藏
Oh, I believe in yesterday
噢，我突然相信昨天